foreign
[Music]
Trevor damn it Fatso this better be a
[__] joke
I'm sorry Knuckles but Bart will be only
rented out three rooms obviously he
wants to Bunk with me and there's no way
I can turn my back on my bro
three people per room remember
I remember
that's nice sweetie but I wasn't talking
to you
oh okay
this is nuts Sonic those two Geeks have
butt sex by the time I unpack the room
will reap of sweaty in her desk Cyrus
just got done bragging about how Trevor
forcefully and non-consensually
miscellaneous objects up his disgusting
ass
I would like to point out that only
sometimes it's against my will
if you're that desperate you could
always ask to switch with one of the
girls
not a goddamn chance Knuckles the cool
Echidna does not bond with [__]
I demand my own room bartlebby literally
just bought this section of Japan
yesterday there's no reason he can't do
it
bartelby is this true are you lying just
so you can sleep with me
well I'd never and might I add I would
have ordered you a room if you asked
nicely that you are being very greedy so
I'm inclined to say no
I see so this is how far our friendship
goes Sonic Hedgehog you know I used to
think you were cool because you were
blue but now I see your true colors
you're not blue you're just a [__]
loser
let's bounce nerds
wow look over there on the bed you guys
it's one of those super expensive hotel
pillowmans I thought they were only
enter Ben Legend Made Up by jealous poor
people
you know the real my green turd colored
friend very real indeed
yeah I know before we go down to the
bath house with other naked guys who
probably peed in the water how about we
play a little game we all race for the
mint and whoever can grab it first gets
to eat it
sounds fun let's do it to it
alrighty let's get ready on your mark
get set
go
[Music]
thank you
I won I won I got here first so that
means I won
my candies
I got to it first
yeah well I grabbed it first
you you only grabbed it first because I
was carrying the luggage I wanted it I
want a yummy hotel and right now
don't cry babe there's more over there
did I say you could speak much go unpack
my [__] you're not getting away from me
ah
yeah
you brothers are big fat smelly cheetahs
I pay for this room I pay for this
entire vacation so that hotel mint was
meant for me and nobody else it was mine
mine mine
well damage you should have been faster
bro stop it he might hit me again
okay then I got a new game we can all
play if you say one more word to me this
entire vacation I am going to give you
the biggest fattest chunkiest beef
stewed on your throat
I'd like to see you
and that's why I think crib should only
be illegal on the weekends
okay I think it should always be illegal
[Music]
hmm no Mindy you're doing it all wrong
you're supposed to use chassix here
watch this
oh and then I stick it up my butt nope
you eat it
Oh sushi is boring I hate the Japanese
[Music]
Flora you idiot you got rice on my two
thousand dollar gluten bag
oops sorry
sorry sorry is that all you have to say
well sorry would be the adequate
response in this scenario yes
dumb ass you ruined it I don't want it
anymore code put it up on eBay to sell
it so I can get money and enlarge my
boobs
the hell that's who she dropped was
totally on purpose
so girlfriend how's the love life going
any guy catch your attitude
don't be silly you know how busy things
have been since I reopened my shop I
simply wouldn't have the time for the
dating life even if I wanted
which is why I wasn't talking to you
head
the Twisted girl what's your game [__]
what are you plotting
yo Cyrus do you want any help removing
your chemo now you will probably have
trouble getting it over your massive
dump truck sized butt
oh that's okay I can get to it myself
what are you drawing there
oh it's nothing give it to me Trevor
wait you mustn't see
now what have we here
huh oh yeah Cyrus these are these are
phenomenal did you draw them when I
wasn't looking
actually those aren't you
as if you know another boy with square
glasses like mine
and huge [__] muscles
I just think you're super cool that's
all
I think it's kind of awesome that you
want to draw me so much I guess I am
quite the looker after all
but you know what's better
these balls
that's right yellow boy
you again what you want now Trevor
literally pulled up his kimono
and he was wearing a goddamn Fantasy on
his skinny ass the traditional Japanese
undergarment four adult males made from
a length of rope
do you believe me that he's gay now
damn I'll have to talk with bartlebby
about getting one of those that sounds
hot no it [__] ain't [__] go tell
your boyfriend to come over and make
them stop being gay Cyrus and Trevor
aren't even dating and Trevor says
sucking balls is gay so he would never
do it
do you enjoy spreading lies about my
pals
those two are clearly banging I'm not
going to spend another second in that
room let me in
ah well we're kind of in the middle of
something right now
what
sarinux but I'm going to close the door
now because you're homophobia and racism
towards hippies are making me really
uncomfortable
thank you
[Music]
what the hell are you doing
fun the key card's not working I think
the girls decided to play a little trick
on me and switched it out for a fake
fake up
well earlier when I swamped the door it
went caught [__] and opened right up it
was so easy then
I simply have no idea why it isn't
working now
um you mean like this
hey I get it I was holding it upside
down
Yonex over here go grab your things
we're heading down to the bath house
well it seems like you got stuff to do
so I won't keep you thanks again for the
help
finally have you cornered white man you
shall not escape from me this time oh no
bartelby is in trouble
don't worry about me I can take him you
too go on ahead and get to safety let's
do what he says we're obviously no match
for him
look he's wearing an orange belt do you
know what that means
the orange belt means you are Level 3
out of 10 in Karate in other words
whoever this [__] kid is they're
seriously no joke yo bro is right for
once my love
Yeah but I like the wind
I expected this moment to come sometime
over the weekend but you showed up
sooner than I anticipated
but know this before you make a fool of
yourself we need not be enemies
you dare to follow me with the hand of
friendship after all you have done was
it not you who bought my older brother's
hotel at a discounted price it was your
own idiotic brother's fault for selling
it half off if you have a bone to pick
it is with him not me
words may work in America but they feel
here in my homeland the only option left
for you is to fight only one of us can
walk away from this dojo
ancient Chinese secret technique of [__]
[Music]
paper bombs I see though your white man
you are knowledgeable in the Japanese
heart of combat perhaps I was quick to
judge you forgive me for not seeing you
as a worthy competent in honor of our
new friendship allow me to Grant you
some wisdom
a war is coming in the future and when
it does it will shake the world take
this ninja informations call don't open
it until the time is right
and when might that be
look to the East and when the sun sets
red and all hope scenes lost that is
when you will know
Excuse me while I put out this paper
bomb
ancient Chinese secret technique gold
waterfall
I have to get naked in front of all the
boys
that's what they do in Japanese cartoons
if I get naked
if you are Greek god
what's the hold up hurry up and get in
the water
yet you are starting to look like a big
smelly baby
I have grown tired of waiting yet enough
so we can compare the size of our
muscles
since you always say your star bigger
suck
you weren't lying to us were you don't
tell me you're just a scrawny dork
I'm not a scrawny dork
then why don't you prove it take off
that kimono before I go over there and
rip it off you myself
why you little bastard you really
thought you could shoot us
you'll know Beefcake like me you're just
immensely toothpick every one point and
laugh at him degrade him and make him
want to commit suicide by killing
himself
thank you
Trevor how could you you just said five
minutes ago that you go to the YMCA
were you lying about that too
yes I don't even know how to spell the
YMCA
do you have a problem with that
you're damn right we got a problem
you're nothing but the language
yeah well at least I know how to swim
no no this isn't about my blueberry baby
this is about you the man who once
claimed to have 32 pack abs
whatever come on Cyrus let's go eat
ramen
I I think I need some time to be alone
[Music]
sit up stupid we can't understand you
blowing bubbles
I was asking how did you and manic start
dating sorry if that's a strange thing
to ask
they that's a good question
literally why the [__] did you even
start going out with my brother of all
people he's so ugly and he smells like
Ranch flavored Dorito chips
I guess I never really gave it much pot
but he does give a pretty decent [__]
come on Mindy there has to be more to it
than that what did he do to make her
heart flutter
what can I say the green beans a bit of
a little trick
he can be a bit persuasive with his
balls if you catch my drift
I didn't know your brother collects
marbles
thank you
seriously first ever craps the bed and
then some [__] decides to go blast
their music at two in the morning
someone's getting their ass [__] beat
[Music]
turn that off [__]
oops sorry did I wake you I just found
this piano in the lobby and wanted to
give it a whirl
can you not some of us are trying to
sleep
I'll only be a minute sorry about that
do you wanna try it
music is for girls and retards Sono I'm
going to take a crap like a real man
does
come on it's not that hard unless you're
you know scared
afraid nonsense Knuckles the cool
Echidna isn't afraid of [__] except
Bartleby
and why don't you prove it
is that a challenge move over [__]
up your gloves
what about them
God you're such a novice how do you
expect to press any of the correct Keys
like that
man hold on I was kidding but you
actually do kind of suck
no I don't this piano is broken it's
probably the cause we are in Japan
what that doesn't make any sense you
idiot
come on Knox you're making it look way
harder than it actually is
here let me I'll show you what to do
[Music]
see it's not that hard right
how are you doing that hard work and
dedication something you wouldn't know
like how can you talk and play at the
same time
I'm just cool like that I guess
you know I really like you a lot and I
feel like you might like me too
but you don't have to say it if you
don't feel like it
not right now anyway I'm pretty
comfortable with the relationship we
have now
sure it's not moving as fast as what
Sonic and Bartleby have
but what I appreciate most is how you're
just a good friend
my part of she's not and do you don't
you get your place is the friend zone
oh [__]
[Music]
would you look at that fireworks
oh bartelby aren't they absolutely
gorgeous
very beautiful indeed however
they would be even more beautiful if
they were blue like your fat ass and
also if it weren't for the approaching
Darkness
you know boys joining the anti-sonic
underground fan club was the best thing
I ever did I didn't have many friends in
LazyTown it's kind of nice having
someone to talk to
oh come on Roti you're going to make us
cry
because pumpkin man I need to be careful
because of kirao there is a good chance
that he poisoned this tomato
in hopes of cutting my life short
in fact I have deducted that it is a 43
that KIRO implanted poison into this
Tomato Seed before it was even
cultivated in the ground in preparation
that one day it would be put on this
Whopper from Burger King
how very clever of Yuki around but I was
again one step ahead of you what now
what other tricks do you have up your
sleeve
by the way heart Guy what's your name
you never did tell us
so it's straight Belle
you idiots what did I tell you about
using your real names
are you saying this is the work of
keyword sokiro is working with a Sonic
Underground
he must have this place bugging somehow
quick look around for a recording device
you heard the Japanese man my fellow
pedophiles get on it stat before we're
all [__] dead
I don't see it not here go look under
the couch God damn it will spread your
butt cheeks
[Music]
that's one down well and I Sonic
Underground how does it feel sucking the
balls of a god of a new world
do my salty balls please you do you like
my sweaty nuts on your face
now hopefully yeah we'll eat that tomato
that I've been growing for eight months
and [__] a Burger King
good job light those [__] have no
idea what they Unleashed now can I have
the sweet red apple you promised me you
said you would give me an Apple if I
planted that tape recorder in the
anti-sonic underground fan club's
hideout
you don't get one what why not because
you still refuse to tell me yell's name
but wait just get the [__] and gummy
your eyes that way you would kill him
how about I give you this instead
[Music]
now do you realize the Dominion I have
over you [__] since only those who
have touched the death know can see you
a god of death I can't fart in your
[__] face anytime I want to
and you can't ask anyone for help or
tell my parents to make me stop
did anyone find it yet
Randy how can you be smiling at times
like this they're going to kill us all
at this rate
silly Rooney I'm smiling because his
death wasn't the loss in fact it was the
opposite it was a game you see
for now we have an open slot to join our
ranks someone far more powerful than him
more powerful Drake now who's today
I would like to introduce the final
member of the anti-sonic underground fan
club
his name is
[Music]
[__] but how can't this be this is
what we get for waiting two [__]
years to start World War III
foreign
what is the meaning of this are you the
new member Randy was talking about
foreign
he he's fast yet yes whatever you save
us just please don't hurt me very good
[Music]
she said
let me know
[Music]
I remember